Personal
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Personal
2.1.1.1.21
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1236
- Personal, 2.1.1.1.21
  - Portrait of Frank R. Roberson, circa 1908; 15; 5x7 (Box 1236)
  - Portrait of Frank R. Roberson, 1908; 16; 5x7 (Box 1236)
  - Portrait of Frank R. Roberson, 1908; 17; 5x7 (Box 1236)
  - Frank R. Roberson (copy), circa 1911; 18; 5x7 (Box 1236)
  - Christmas card (copy), 1913; 19; 5x7 (Box 1236)
  - Christmas card, 1913; 20; 5x7 (Box 1236)
  - Bell, Christmas card, 1913; 21; 5x7 (Box 1236)
  - Copy for Christmas card (not used), before 1916; 22; 5x7 (Box 1236)
  - Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson in front of fountain, before 1916; 23; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson in front of building, Italy, before 1916; 24; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson in carriage, before 1916; 25; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson surrounded by pigeons, before 1916; 26; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson surrounded by pigeons, before 1916; 27; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson and an unidentified man, before 1916; 28; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson sitting on wall, before 1916; 29; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson, before 1916; 30; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson in ornate building, before 1916; 31; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson sitting by ruins, before 1916; 32; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson sitting by ruins, before 1916; 33; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson [?] in front of ruins, before 1916; 34; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Unidentified man sitting in chair, before 1916; 35; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Frank R. Roberson and men changing tire, before 1916; 36; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Frank R. Roberson and men changing tire, before 1916; 37; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Frank R. Roberson watching automobile being lifted onto ship, before 1916; 38; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Frank R. Roberson with camera taking picture of children, before 1916; 39; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Frank R. Roberson and woman, before 1916; 40; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Frank R. Roberson watching automobile being lifted onto ship, before 1916; 41; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Frank R. Roberson looking over ship railing, before 1916; 42; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Frank R. Roberson and small child, before 1916; 43; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Frank R. Roberson sitting with children, before 1916; 44; 4x5 film (Box 1236)
  - Frank R. Roberson, copy, 1913 February 20; 45; 4x5 (Box 1236)
  - Frank R. Roberson and Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson, copy, 1913 February 20; 46; 4x5 (Box 1236)
  - Frank R. Roberson and party in automobile, before 1916; 47; 5x7 (Box 1236)
  - Frank R. Roberson and party in automobile, before 1916; 48; 5x7 (Box 1236)